Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Editorial Records 1948-1983, undated (bulk 1959-1979) MS 3009-RG 6.I MS 3009-RG 6TEST
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Editor-in-Chief: Subseries I.B. Henry Anatole Grunwald Files, 1944-1998 (bulk 1968-1987); 74.0 Linear feet; (74 boxes)
  - Subsubseries I.B.3. Departmental Files, 1946-1987; 25.0 Linear feet; (25 boxes)
    - 1983: Fred Jerome: SIPI (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 21)
    - 1983: Edit Pour (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 1)
    - 1983: Time Panel at Foreign Policy Association Luncheon (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 2)
    - 1983: Discover Redesign (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 3)
    - 1983: Secular Trend Society (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 4)
    - 1983: Haidee Granger: First Ladies Program (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 5)
    - 1983: Council on Foreign Relations: USSR [Union of Soviet Socialist Republics] and United States Relations-Reagan (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 6-7)
    - 1983: George Shultz Breakfast (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 8)
    - 1983: Time Japan Issue (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 9)
    - 1983: Fortune Task Force (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 10)
    - 1983: HBO [Home Box Office] and Cinemax Programming (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 11)
    - 1983: 60th Anniversary Issue (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 12)
    - 1984: Legal [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1984: McManus: Long-Term Incentive Plan Package (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 13)
    - 1984: Affirmative Action (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 14)
    - 1984: Minutes of Tuesday Group Meetings (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 15)
    - 1984: American-Austrian Foundation (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 16)
    - 1984: Lally Weymouth Clippings (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 17)
    - 1984: Ralph Graves Farewell Party (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 18)
      1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "Ralph Graves - Ret." On accompanying note: "Save Ralph Tape."
    - 1984: Notes on Breakfast with Chinese Prime Minister (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 19)
    - 1984: Management Meeting: Troutbeck (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 20)
    - 1984: Magazine Development (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 21-22)
    - 1984: Fuerbringer on Leisure (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 23)
    - 1984: Staff Magazine Suggestions (Offsite-box 1036, Folder 24-26)
      Contains ideas submitted to the Magazine Development Group received after Grunwald put out an invitation to all Time Inc. staff for new magazine suggestions.
    - 1984: Investment Week (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 1-2)
    - 1984: Quality (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 3)
    - 1984: Daniels' Woman Weekly Prospectus (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 4)
    - 1984: Leisure (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 5)
    - 1984: Yesterday Proposal (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 6)
    - 1984: Home Office (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 7)
    - 1984: Quality Essay for Annual Report (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 8)
    - 1984: Corporate Identity Study: Yankelovich (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 9)
    - 1984: Distinguished Speakers Program: Ronald Reagan and Geraldine Ferraro (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 10)
    - 1984: Employee Opinion Survey: Hiland-Graves Memos (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 11)
    - 1984: Staff Breakdowns for All Magazines (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 12)
    - 1984: Scientists' Institute for Public Information [SIPI] (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 13-14)
    - 1984: Teddy White: Time Agreement: Making of the President (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 15)
    - 1984: Teddy White: Time Agreement: Making of the President [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1984: Armand Hammer Lunch (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 16)
    - 1984: Armand Hammer Introduction at Council on Foreign Relations Dinner (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 17)
    - 1984: Correspondence with Subbotin and Ivanko of Novosty Regarding Interview with Gorbachev (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 18)
    - 1984: Clifton Wharton Lunch (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 19)
    - 1984: Remarks at Korean Dinner: 21 Club (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 20)
    - 1984: Discover Edit Conference: Troutbeck (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 21)
    - 1984: Money Sales Meeting: Round Hill, Jamaica (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 22)
    - 1984: Al Haig Dinner: 21 Club (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 23)
    - 1984: Woman Weekly Prospectus (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 24)
    - 1984: Overtime (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 25)
    - 1984: Temple-Inland Board Dinner (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 26)
    - 1984: Georgy Arbatov Lunch: Council on Foreign Relations (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 27)
    - 1984: Raul Yzaguirre (La Raza) Meeting (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 28)
    - 1984: Gloria Steinem Benefit Dinner (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 29)
    - 1984: Bohemian Grove (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 30)
    - 1984: Introduction at Sakharov Screening: Kennedy Center (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 31)
    - 1984: Centrism (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 32)
    - 1984: Cruise on Malcom Forbes' Highlander (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 33)
    - 1984: Felix Rohatyn-Alvin Ailey Dinner (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 34)
    - 1984: Letters to Convention Delegates (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 35)
    - 1984: Democratic Convention: San Francisco (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 36)
    - 1984: Republican National Convention: Dallas (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 37)
    - 1984: Hideaway Reports (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 38)
    - 1984: McKinsey Report on Repositioning Discover to Achieve Success and Dave Maness's Summary (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 39)
    - 1984: Discover White Paper (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 40)
    - 1984: United States-Soviet Symposium (Offsite-box 1037, Folder 41)
    - 1984: Corporate Circulation Conference: Martha's Vineyard (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 1)
    - 1984: Wyandanch Retreat (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 2)
    - 1984: Munro's Non-Executive Briefing (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 3)
    - 1984: Managing Editors Lunch at La Cote Basque (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 4)
    - 1984: "Nobody Loves the Press. Whom Does the Press Love?" (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 5)
    - 1984: Libel (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 6)
    - 1984: Expense Reports (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 7)
    - 1984: Possible Dreams Auction: Martha's Vineyard (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 8)
    - 1984: The Story of Great Music (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 9a)
    - 1984: Foreign Affairs Article (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 9b)
    - 1985: Legal (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 10)
    - 1985: Legal [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1985: Headcount Reduction (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 11)
    - 1985: Headcount Reduction [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1985: Stock Option Grant Recommendations (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 12)
    - 1985: LTIP/AIP Evaluations [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1985: Affirmative Action (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 13)
    - 1985: Tuesday Group Meetings (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 14)
    - 1985: Magazine Development (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 15)
    - 1985: Skunkworks (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 16)
      A proposed department to develop smaller magazines.
    - 1985: Staff Magazine Suggestions (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 17)
    - 1985: Asia Week (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 18)
    - 1985: Total Health (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 19)
    - 1985: Press Folder (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 20)
    - 1985: Advance Magazine (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 21)
    - 1985: Picture Week (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 22-23)
    - 1985: Quality (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 24-25)
    - 1985: Leisure (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 26)
    - 1985: Overtime (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 27)
    - 1985: Inauguration (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 28)
    - 1985: Distinguished Speakers Program: Brian Mulroney (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 29)
    - 1985: Time Hollywood Cover Show (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 30)
    - 1985: Trip to India (Offsite-box 1038, Folder 31)
    - 1985: Leadership Essay for Annual Report (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 1)
    - 1985: "Update '85" (Canadian News Tour in Washington) (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 2)
    - 1985: Annual Report Essay Drafts (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 3)
    - 1985: Attitudes Toward Discover (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 4)
    - 1985: First Amendment Audit (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 5)
    - 1985: Council Study Group on TV News and American Foreign Policy (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 6)
    - 1985: American Council on Germany: Dallas (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 7)
    - 1985: Corporate Public Affairs Conference: Ponte Vedra, FL (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 8)
    - 1985: Press Leaks (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 9)
    - 1985: Scientists' Institute for Public Information (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 10)
    - 1985: Time Sales Meeting: Phoenix (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 11)
    - 1985: Time Distinguished Speakers Program (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 12)
    - 1985: Hollywood Exhibit and Essay (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 13)
    - 1985: World Press Freedom Committee (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 14)
    - 1985: People Treatment of HBO (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 15)
    - 1985: American Association of Advertising Agencies Talk: Greenbrier, WV (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 16)
    - 1985: Pre-Board Dinner (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 17)
    - 1985: Editor-in-Chief Notes (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 18)
    - 1985: Munro's Executive Briefing: Lyford Cay (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 19)
    - 1985: Southern Living Meeting: Sandestin, FL (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 20)
    - 1985: Clare Boothe Luce Dinner (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 21)
    - 1985: Discover: New Direction (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 22)
    - 1985: Retrofit [of the Time & Life Building] (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 23)
    - 1985: Letters Regarding Immigrants Essay (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 24-25)
    - 1985: Foreign Policy Association: Bipartisan Foreign Policy Panel (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 26)
    - 1985: Advisory Committee on The Council's National Role (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 27)
    - 1985: Immigration Essay Research (Offsite-box 1039, Folder 28)
    - 1985: Ruth Brine's 40th Anniversary Lunch (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 1)
    - 1985: Gorbachev Interview (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 2)
    - 1985: Talk to CM&D [Corporate Manufacturing & Distribution] Group (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 3)
    - 1985: Campaign for the Council on Foreign Relations (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 4)
    - 1985: Time Edit Process Presentation to the Board of Directors (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 5)
    - 1985: American Austrian Foundation (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 6)
    - 1985: Managing Editor Christmas Lunch: Lutece (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 7)
    - 1985: Time Inc. History Volume 3 (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 8-11)
    - 1985: Cave-McManus Party (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 12)
    - 1985: Wyandanch III (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 13)
    - 1985: Expense Reports (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 14-15)
    - 1985: Possible Dreams Auction (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 16)
    - 1985: Sharon vs. Time: Miscellaneous Correspondence and Reaction (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 17-20)
    - 1985: Sharon vs. Time: Miscellaneous Correspondence and Reaction [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1985: " Time/Canada Update on America '85" (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 21-22)
    - 1985: " Time/Canada Update on America '85": Binder Cover (Offsite-box 1056, Folder 4)
    - 1986: Renata Adler: New Yorker Article (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 23)
    - 1986: Legal [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1986: Bonus File [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R19)
    - 1986: Staff Cuts (Offsite-box 1040, Folder 24)
    - 1986: Staff Cuts [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R19)
    - 1986: Role of the Editor-in-Chief (Offsite-box 1040-1041)
    - 1986: Role of the Editor-in-Chief [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R19)
    - 1986: International Center of Photography Gala (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 2)
    - 1986: Remarks: Editors Meeting (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 3-5)
      1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On side A label: "1. Thornhill Constable Evans." On side B label: "2. Evans contd Constable Silverman."
      1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On side A label: "3. end of Evans - table noise Cunningham Jason McManus begins." On side B label: "4. McManus - Ryan Loeb Daniels."
      1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On side A label: "Lunch 1st 1/2 P. Ryan-transcibed." On case: "1st 1/2 P. Ryan lunch."
      1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On side A label: "5. General Discussion O'Neill-Asia Week." On side B label: "6. Clark Schiller."
      1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On side A label: "7. General talk [poss] Schiller cost cutting." On side B label: "8. General talk about cost cutting."
      1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On side A label: "9." On side B label: "21 Club."
    - 1986: Board of Editors Lunch (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 6)
    - 1986: Board of Editors Dinner: 21 Club (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 7)
    - 1986: Talk at Senior Editors Dinner (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 8)
      1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On side A label: "Grunwald/Brack Remarks Edit Briefing Dinner December 11, 1986."
    - 1986: Edit Staff Lunch (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 9)
      1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On side A label: "Grunwald/Brack Remarks Editorial Briefing Lunch December 19, 1986."
    - 1986: Expense Accounts (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 10)
    - 1986: Time Australia (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 11)
    - 1986: Quality (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 12-13)
    - 1986: Quality Reaction (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 14)
    - 1986: Leisure (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 15)
    - 1986: Parenting (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 16)
    - 1986: Picture Week Preview to Board Meeting (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 17)
    - 1986: Picture Week (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 18-19)
    - 1986: Magazine Development (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 20)
    - 1986: First Amendment Audit (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 21)
    - 1986: First Amendment Audit [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R19)
    - 1986: Rethinking the Newsmagazine (Offsite-box 1041, Folder 22)
    - 1986: Council on Foreign Relations: US-USSR Study Group (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 1)
    - 1986: Guild Negotiations (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 2)
    - 1986: Pumpkin Papers Irregulars (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 3)
    - 1986: American-Austrian Foundation (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 4)
    - 1986: Distinguished Speakers Program and Grunwald's Introduction of President Corazon Aquino (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 5)
    - 1986: Time Inc. International Operations (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 6)
    - 1986: Scientists' Institute for Public Information (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 7-8)
    - 1986: Domestic Bureau Chiefs Meeting: Chicago (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 9)
    - 1986: Hollywood Exhibit (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 10)
    - 1986: Edit Staff Dinner (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 11)
    - 1986: Curricula and Textbooks (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 12)
    - 1986: Edit Staff Dinner (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 13)
    - 1986: Democracy Essay (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 14)
    - 1986: Strategic Defense Initiative Conference: Washington, D.C. (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 15)
    - 1986: Bill Rukeyser Dinner: Four Seasons (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 16)
    - 1986: Life Futures Meeting: Norwich, CT (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 17)
    - 1986: Rob Durkee's Sales Development Program (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 18)
    - 1986: Letter to Outside Directors Regarding Lunch (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 19)
    - 1986: Life 50th Anniversary Gala (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 20)
    - 1986: South African Newstour (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 21)
    - 1986: Board of Editors (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 22)
    - 1986: European and Middle Eastern Bureau Chiefs Meeting: Paris (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 23-24)
    - 1986: Possible Dreams Auction: Martha's Vineyard (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 25)
    - 1986: Miscellaneous Memos: May-September and Grunwald Journal [entries] for Possible Book (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 26-28)
    - 1986: Life Futures Meeting Binder (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 29)
    - 1986: Picture Week Review (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 30)
    - 1986: John Fairfax and Sons Joint Venture [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R19)
    - 1986: Council Discussion Group: National Objectives and Priorities in American Foreign Policy (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 31)
    - 1986: Great American Newsstand (Offsite-box 1055, Item 5)
      Contains an audio reel and floppy disk in one audio reel box.
      1 audiotape reel: analog; 10 1/2 in., 1/4 in. tape. On label: "Time Inc. Great American Newsstand. Audio 1+2. Data 3. Clock 4." On container label: "Client: Hollowtree. Title: Time Inc. Grunwald Pres. Date: 2/18/87."
      1 computer disc (floppy disk): 5 1/4 in. On label: "5/20/86. SOR 86. Soty 85. EATLIFE. CSA Exec." On disc sleeve: "CSA Executive. 5/20/86. NSY-86. State of Retailing '86. Great American Newsstand."
    - 1987: Council: Kissinger-Vance Group Session #3 (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 32)
    - 1987: Conference: Kissinger-Vance Meeting (Offsite-box 1042, Folder 33)
    - 1987: Discussion Group Meetings: Background Papers and Correspondence to Cyrus Vance and Kissinger (Offsite-box 1042-1043)
    - 1987: Travel in China and Korea (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 2-3)
    - 1987: Article for Russian Paper (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 4)
    - 1987: United States-Japan Trade Relations Roundtable: Fortune and Time Editors (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 5)
    - 1987: Memos and Press Coverage of McManus-Cave-Grunwald Memo (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 6)
    - 1987: Discover Publishing Review (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 7)
    - 1987: Goal Setting (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 8)
    - 1987: Marty Gardner Task Forces [Marketing, Business, Travel and Entertainment] (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 9)
    - 1987: NYC Opera Guild Auction: Time Cover Winner (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 10)
    - 1987: Lunch: Time Forums (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 11)
    - 1987: Korea Study Group (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 12-13)
    - 1987: Discover Memo to Board (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 14)
    - 1987: Center for Communication Lunch (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 15)
    - 1987: Presidents' Articles for Life (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 16)
    - 1987: Gorbachev (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 17)
    - 1987: Managing Editor Stock Grants (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 18)
    - 1987: United States Constitution Issue (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 19)
    - 1987: New Executive Position: Stolley (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 20)
    - 1987: Editorial Guidelines Manual (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 21)
    - 1987: History of Time Newstours (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 22)
    - 1987: Newstour to Russia (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 23)
    - 1987: Russia/___ Background (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 24)
    - 1987: Law Speech, Privacy, Etc. (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 25)
    - 1987: Articles Regarding Grunwald, 1968-1987 (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 26-27)
    - 1987: United States Senate Committee on Foreign Relations: Opening Statement of Grunwald, Statements to Committee, Grunwald Biography (Offsite-box 1043, Folder 28)
      Materials regarding Grunwald's ambassador appointment confirmation hearing.
    - 1987: Biography (Offsite-box 1044, Folder 1)
    - 1987: Terrorism Conference: Washington, D.C. (Offsite-box 1044, Folder 2)
    - 1987: Transcript of Discover Terrorism Conference (Offsite-box 1044, Folder 3)
    - 1987: AIP Evaluation Forms (Offsite-box 1044, Folder 4)
    - 1987: Mortimer Adler PBS Show: Raleigh and Durham, NC (Offsite-box 1044, Folder 5)
    - 1987: Interview with Italian Magazine Epoca (Offsite-box 1044, Folder 6)
    - 1987: Introduction fo Colby and Turner: Council on Foreign Relations (Offsite-box 1044, Folder 7)
    - 1987: Magazine Issues Q&A (Offsite-box 1044, Folder 8)
    - 1987: Flicky Ford Project (Offsite-box 1044, Folder 9)
    - 1987: Revised Executive Bonus Plans (Offsite-box 1044, Folder 10)
    - 1987: Annual Report (Offsite-box 1044, Folder 11)
    - 1987: Quality (Offsite-box 1044, Folder 12)
    - 1987: World Press Freedom Committee: Censorship Conference: London (Offsite-box 1044, Folder 13)
    - 1987: Dinner with Soviet Editors (Offsite-box 1044, Folder 14a)
    - Undated: Essay Notes: Requiem in Leningrad (Offsite-box 1044, Folder 14b)
- Series I. Editor-in-Chief: Subseries I.C. Jason McManus Files
  Organized into four subsubseries:
  Subsubseries I.C.1. Chron File
  Subsubseries I.C.2. Correspondence
  Subsubseries I.C.3. Departmental Files
  Subsubseries I.C.4. Trips
  Jason McManus started at Time Inc. in 1957 as a Sports Illustrated summer trainee. The next year, he was a Time-Life News Service trainee. Time Inc. hired him in 1959, and he held various writing and editor positions with Time through 1974, including launching the European edition. In 1976, he was promoted to Time Assistant Managing Editor then Time Executive Editor in 1978. From 1982 to 1983, the corporate editorial department selected him to serve a temporary assignment with that office as Assistant Corporate Editor while continuing to hold his permanent position. After this temporary position, he served one year as Corporate Editor then two years as Time Managing Editor before his appointment as Editor-in-Chief in 1987. McManus retired from Time Inc. in 1994.
  The Jason McManus Files primarily are during his tenure as Editor-in-Chief with some records from earlier in his career. Records include his day-to-day file, correspondence, departmental files, and travel records.
  - Subsubseries I.C.1. Chron File, 1992-1993
    The Chron File is McManus's record of day-to-day memos and other correspondence sent out from his office. The contents of the folders are arranged in reverse chronological order. Memos are primarily addressed to All Staff, Reginald Brack (President, CEO, and Chairman), Don Logan (President and CEO), and heads of various departments.
    Organized chronologically.
    - 1992: Memos (Offsite-box 1200, Folder 9-12)
    - 1992: Letters (Offsite-box 1200, Folder 13-16)
    - 1992: Memos to Managing Editors (Offsite-box 1200, Folder 17)
    - 1993: Memos (Offsite-box 1200-1201)
    - 1993: Letters (Offsite-box 1201, Folder 5-8)
  - Subsubseries I.C.2. Memoranda and Correspondence, 1976-1991; 2.5 Linear feet; (3 boxes)
    Organized into Memoranda, arranged alphabetically with General at the front, and Correspondence, arranged chronologically.
    Correspondence contains McManus's incoming and outgoing correspondence. Topics include staff changes, responses to invitations, complaints and responses regarding articles, and general exchanges with other companies and organizations. No folder for 1983 found.
    - Memos: General Outgoing, 1969-1991 (Offsite-box 1201, Folder 9-13)
    - Memoranda: To Ray Cave, 1986 (Offsite-box 1201, Folder 14)
    - Memoranda: To Henry Grunwald, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1201, Folder 15-16)
    - Memos: To Managing Editors, 1984-1993 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 1-3)
    - Memos: To Staff, 1981-1994 (Offsite-box 1201, Folder 17-20)
    - 1981 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 4)
    - 1982 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 5)
    - 1984 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 6)
    - 1985 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 7)
    - 1986 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 8-9)
    - Time Managing Editor Congratulations, 1986 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 10)
    - 1987 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 11-14)
    - Editor-in-Chief Notes of Congratulations, 1987 (Offsite-box 1202-1203)
    - 1988 (Offsite-box 1203, Folder 2-6)
    - 1989 (Offsite-box 1203, Folder 7-11)
    - 1990 (Offsite-box 1203, Folder 12-16)
    - 1991 (Offsite-box 1203-1204)
  - Subsubseries I.C.3. Departmental Files
    Organized alphabetically.